export const questions = [
  { question: 'How many ADULTS are in your household?', type: 'radio', answers: 'number' },
  { question: 'How many CHILDREN UNDER 18?', type: 'radio', answers: 'number' },
  { question: 'What Race do you most identify with? (SELECT ONLY ONE)', type: 'radio', answers: 'ethnicity' },
  { question: 'Have you served in the U.S. Armed Forces?', type: 'radio', answers: 'general' },
  { question: 'How long have you been continuously homeless this time?', type: 'radio', answers: 'number' },
  { question: 'How many times have you been homeless in the past 3 years?', type: 'radio', answers: 'homelessDate' },
  { question: 'Were you on the street, beach, park, or in an emergency shelter each time?', type: 'radio', answers: 'homelessCount' },
  { question: 'Do you have a mental health disability that limits your ability to work or perform activities of daily living?', type: 'radio', answers: 'general' },
  { question: 'Do you have an alcohol or drug problem that limits your ability to work or perform activities of daily living?', type: 'radio', answers: 'general' },
  { question: 'Select all Benefits that you are currently receiving:', type: 'checkbox', answers: 'benefits' },
  { question: 'Do you have a physical, developmental, or other disability that limits your ability to work or perform activities of daily living?', type: 'radio', answers: 'general' }
];
